Narrator: 2
A: England, English
Narrator: 4
B: Ireland, Irish
Narrator: 1
A: Spain, Spanish
Narrator: 3
B: Türkiye, Turkish
Narrator: 7
A: Germany, German
Narrator: 5
B: Mexico, Mexican
Narrator: 8
A: Morocco, Moroccan
Narrator: 6
B: the United States, American
Narrator: 13
A: Argentina, Argentinian
Narrator: 17
B: Australia, Australian
Narrator: 9
A: Brazil, Brazilian
Narrator: 18
B: Canada, Canadian
Narrator: 11
A: Egypt, Egyptian
Narrator: 15
B: India, Indian
Narrator: 12
A: Italy, Italian
Narrator: 16
B: Nigeria, Nigerian
Narrator: 10
A: Peru, Peruvian
Narrator: 14
B: Russia, Russian
Narrator: 20
A: China, Chinese
Narrator: 19
B: Japan, Japanese
Narrator: 21
A: Vietnam, Vietnamese
Narrator: 24
B: the Czech Republic, Czech
Narrator: 22
A: France, French
Narrator: 23
B: Thailand, Thai